<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist>
  <schema path="/com/canonical/unity/thumbnailer/" id="com.canonical.Unity.Thumbnailer">
    <key type="s" name="dash-ubuntu-com-key">
      <default>"0f450aa882a6125ebcbfb3d7f7aa25bc"</default>
      <summary>API key for dash.ubuntu.com service</summary>
      <description>API key for dash.ubuntu.com service</description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="full-size-cache-size">
      <default>50</default>
      <summary>Size of the full-size image cache in megabytes</summary>
      <description>The full-size cache is used to store full-size extracted media artwork and downloaded album art.</description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="thumbnail-cache-size">
      <default>100</default>
      <summary>Size of the thumbnail image cache in megabytes</summary>
      <description>The thumbnail image cache stores scaled thumbnail images.</description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="failure-cache-size">
      <default>2</default>
      <summary>Size of the failure cache in megabytes</summary>
      <description>The failure cache records information about failed downloads or failed thumbnail extractions.</description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="max-thumbnail-size">
      <default>1920</default>
      <summary>Maximum size in pixels for a thumbnail</summary>
      <description>
        Requests for thumbnails larger than this will automatically reduce the thumbnail to max-thumbnail-size in the larger dimension. An exception are requests for local thumbnails with size 0x0, which are returned in their original size.
     </description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="retry-not-found-hours">
      <default>168</default>
      <summary>Time to wait before re-trying for remote artwork that did not exist</summary>
      <description>
        If artwork cannot be retrieved because the remote server authoritavely confirmed that no artwork exists for an artist and album, this parameter defines how long the thumbnailer waits before trying to download the same image again. The default is 168 hours (one week).
     </description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="retry-error-hours">
      <default>2</default>
      <summary>Time to wait before re-trying remote artwork that failed to download</summary>
      <description>
        If artwork cannot be retrieved from the remote server due to an unexpected error (such as the server not responding), this parameter defines how long the thumbnailer waits before trying to download the same image again. The default is two hours.
     </description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="max-downloads">
      <default>8</default>
      <summary>Maximum number of concurrent downloads</summary>
      <description>
        This parameter sets the maximum number of concurrent downloads for remote artwork.
     </description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="max-extractions">
      <default>0</default>
      <summary>Maximum number of concurrent image extractions</summary>
      <description>
        This parameter sets the maximum number of concurrent image extractions from local video files. The default value is zero, which sets the value according to the number of CPU cores.
     </description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="extraction-timeout">
      <default>10</default>
      <summary>Maximum amount of time to wait for an image extraction or download (in seconds)</summary>
      <description>
        This parameter sets the amount of time (in seconds) to wait for a remote image download or a thumbnail extraction before giving up.
     </description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="max-backlog">
      <default>10</default>
      <summary>Maximum number of pending DBus requests before the thumbnailer starts queuing them.</summary>
      <description>
        This parameter limits the number of pending DBus requests to the thumbnailer service. If the number of concurrent requests exceeds the backlog, additional requests are queued and sent once the backlog drops below the limit.
     </description>
    </key>

    <key type="b" name="trace-client">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Enable client-side tracing.</summary>
      <description>
        If set to true, this parameter enables request tracing via qDebug() on the client side.
     </description>
    </key>

    <key type="i" name="log-level">
      <default>1</default>
      <summary>Sets the level of detail of log messages written to stderr.</summary>
      <description>
        At the default setting (1), cache misses are logged, but no messages are written for cache hits. At setting 2, cache hits are logged as well. At setting 0, most messages that are part of normal operation are suppressed. Errors and other unusual operating conditions are always logged, regardless of the logging level.
     </description>
    </key>
  </schema>
</schemalist>
